this is the time known as the great pirate era a countless array of pirates go to battle across
the seas in search of the one piece the legendary treasure left behind by gold roger king of the
pirates monkey d luffy a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit set sail to
become the next king of the pirates as luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles they capture
the unwanted attention of the world government which will use any means necessary to stop them
can't wait to see what kind of adventures up next with a charted course awash in danger and intrigue
the crew will come a path across the grand line to the new world
after the straw hat crew rescued camey from being sold at an auction house they unexpectedly met
brady the craftsman they've been searching for he revealed see the captain turned himself in
while they may execute me i won't die if anyone wants my treasure then it's yours for the take
go find it i left everything i gathered in one place oh in that case let me ask you do you think
you can do it the new world far surpasses anything you can imagine your foes will be powerful knowing
that you still think you can rule this mighty sea what i don't want to rule anything being king of
the pirates is about being more free than anyone i see
no escape admiral kizaru's lightspeed kick
be careful yeah take care of yourselves
we will you do the same
tell hachi goodbye bye guys
isn't this a bit much it's only three days
that doesn't matter goodbyes are always difficult
well i suppose i should be off too
it's been a whirlwind ever since we got here and i wasn't expecting to run into roger's vice
captain i'm kind of stunned
i mean what are the odds he's a pretty intimidating guy for an old geezer i'll give him that much
well he is the most famous man in roger's crew and deservedly so it seems
so that's what crewmen on the odo jackson were like huh
giving a hand to that roger guy is something i'll never forget
in fact it's something i take great pride in
man i'm glad i got to meet him
you know i never would have pegged you for someone who had such reverence for your elders
yeah well sometimes i do okay now shut the hell up
hey i've got an idea
let's go to the amusement park
bad idea
do you even get what's happening
you still haven't learned your lesson have you
sounds like fun
not you too
it's that whole keys on you
we gotta get the hell out of here
don't let those pirates escape
hello
there are wanted men everywhere on this archipelago
look out for the ones worth over 100 million
hello this is admiral kizaru
hmm that's odd
hello
well that's awful strange
crap we're screwed now
no hold on there's still a chance
i think i can get the drop on him and take him down from here
and if i do i'll be famous
huh are you out of your damn mind this is one of the strongest guys in the marines we're talking about
hello
hello do you read me
now take this
oh wait stop
hello
no way
i'll get you this time
what the hell
i know i didn't miss him that time
the bullet passed right through his head
so terribly odd
he's obviously got some kind of crazy devil fruit powers
guns aren't gonna work on him
run for it
pardon me but i was wondering if you could help me out
i'm here looking for a man named sento maru you see
he's a subordinate of mine do you know him
gee all i did was ask them a question
huh
i think admiral kizaru went a hair overboard
he knows better than to break the hustle muscle mangroves
oh wow
i forget my own strength sometimes
ah
talk about crazy
that's admiral kizaru i take it
please apu this is dangerous for us too we really need to get out of here
you fool
what fun is there in slinking away it's better to run after you've pissed your enemy off
then what are you planning to do
come on pick up the pace
man a lot of them got away
yeah they were just too many
ah
It was Jewelry Bonnie!
She's got a bounty of 140 million!
Which do you prefer, young or old?
What happened?
Hello? Hello, please respond!
Watch out for the rookie pirate's worth over 100 million!
I repeat, watch out for the rookie pirate's worth over 100 million!
I know you! You're Capone gang-bang, and you've got 138 million Barry Bounty!
No way you're sailing out of here!
What, did your crew run off and leave you?
Too bad for you! Hands in the air!
Huh. In terms of tough, guys, you boys are outmatched.
What's all this about?
Captain Hawkins!
There's no reason to worry.
Fate has already been decided.
Ooh, excuse me, but I was wondering if you fellas could help me out.
We'll keep him busy for you, Captain.
Please, sir. You need to get out of here.
No need to panic.
I won't be dying today.
How do you like that?
Toasty enough?
Step aside.
We'll handle this.
That hurt! What do you get it out of?
Room.
Shambles.
Gotcha.
Oh, the pain!
So irritating.
How about this?
And that's the end of that nuisance.
You just don't know when to quit, do you?
The best place to hide is in the amusement park.
You're so full of it.
You just want to screw around and have fun.
You just want to keep going.
No.
It can't be.
Who is this guy?
Enemy attack!
Hurry up!
Go!
Commence the attack!
Get those cannons ready!
Open the gunplots!
Commence bombardment!
What?
Fire!
This is crazy!
Something is flying out of his chest!
Oh, he's moved!
What the hell just happened?
He didn't even have to lift a finger!
Gallery!
Charge!
Hey, look at his stomach!
Something's coming out!
Soldiers on horseback!
Come on!
That's ridiculous!
I don't know how that power works, but I think I'm starting to see why they call him the gang!
Firing squad, take aim!
Watch with the smoke!
Father, take it easy!
It's too much!
Told ya.
You'll need more troops than that.
Get outta here!
I still haven't gotten enough to eat.
Don't worry about it.
I'm sure there'll be good food on the next island, too.
Did you hear the news?
One of the seven warlords has joined the attack.
Wait, are you serious?
Which one of them is it?
A warlord.
I was expecting an admiral, but not you, too.
I guess it was too much to ask to sneak past Navy headquarters.
How unfortunate!
My pride won't let me walk away.
Captain, please, you must escape.
It's far too dangerous here.
Captain Hawkins, what are you...
Combat.
Chance of defeat, 100%.
Pardon, but could you help me?
Escape.
Chance of success, 12%.
I'm looking for a man named Sentomaru.
Do you know him?
Defense.
Chance of evasion, 76%.
Hello?
I know of no such man.
Go ask someone else.
Well, if I can't find him, that leaves me with a bit of spare time, you see.
And if I have some spare time, I obviously can't let a wanted man escape.
Especially one with a 249 million berry bounty, magician Basil Hawkins.
Speed is weight.
Observe.
This is what it feels like to be kicked at the speed of light.
Captain!
Looks like we're finally ready to set sail.
Great, then let's get out of here.
What the...
What happened?
Are...
Are we under attack?
I don't know.
He just suddenly went flying.
Look at that.
He's strong.
Hey.
Wait.
What's he doing now?
What's he doing?
Alright.
Let's go.
Let's go!
Get out of here!
Looks like we're finally ready to set sail.
Great, then let's get out of here.
What the...
What happened?
Are...
Are we under attack?
I don't know, he just suddenly went flying.
Look at that, he's strong.
Hey, wait, what's he doing now?
I didn't see anyone. He just burst into flames.
Who attacked? And from where?
Huh?
What was that?
Impressive. You far surpassed what I imagined.
Now, ain't that weird?
To think two would be destroyed already.
Against an admiral such as yourself, I might feel nervous even with ten.
Hold on. Is that the Mad Monka Rouge?
And he's not alone, either.
That's Bartholomew Kuma, one of the seven warlords of the sea.
You're strong. I'll give you that much.
There's a foe even stronger than him.
Kizaru! No!
How unfortunate. I have a navy admiral ahead of me and a warlord behind. I'm finished!
Not necessarily. I don't see the shadow of death upon you.
Oh? Is that so? Hawkins of the North Blue.
Thanks for the tip, foe though you may be.
Oh, good. It looks like someone else decided to join the fight.
Is that...?
Red Flag Diaz Drake. Why's he here?
Is that the extent of your power, Mad Monk?
Mad Monk?
Ah, it's you again.
Huh. Rear Admiral Drake.
Ah, crap. I hadn't planned on running into Kizaru.
I've taken quite a beating. But let's see if Hawkins' prediction is true or not.
There might be some hope for me yet.
Let's start this over nice and slow.
Look at this! This is insane! Unbelievable! I've got a blast here!
You're insane! Whoever stays here is gonna die! This is our chance to escape!
Ah, you're no fun!
We're here to party and that's Captain's orders.
Who the heck are you?
Get back, Luffy!
He's one of the seven warlords of the sea!
He is? How do you guys know that?
Luffy, don't let that attack hit you! It's a shockwave!
What?
Damn!
What is that?
Great! So he can do this crap too?
Hey! You lied! That wasn't a shockwave!
That was... a beam!
You're gonna be impressed straight to your grave!
Bartholomew Kuma, why are you here?
That bastard!
Hey, I remember him now!
He's the guy that showed up at Thriller Bark I never fought!
That's right, the very same!
Things got pretty dicey when he started shooting at us with shockwaves from the paws on his hands!
We barely made it out alive!
The fact that we are still alive is probably the reason he came back!
In other words, we got lucky last time, but he's here to finish the job!
Sure, that's one way to look at it, but I call this payback time!
You dead?
You got him!
Not exactly. He's down, but he ain't out.
Alright, second gear!
We know he's strong, no question!
So let's go all out from the start!
I'll be on the boat!
Something's off here.
He seems different from the last time we met.
Or am I crazy?
Let's go!
What's taking so long?
The warship should have been here by now.
Why hasn't Uncle Kizaru contacted me yet?
It's chaos already.
He'd better hurry.
Or there won't be any rookies left.
Not at this rate.
At this rate.
You met this warlord guy before, but this time he's different?
Yeah, the real one had different powers and he was a lot more talkative.
That's not what I want to hear.
This guy's damn near invincible and you're telling me there's two of him?
Wait, so this one's a fake?
On the next, One Piece.
Overwhelming.
The Navy's fighting weapons, the pacifistas.
I'm gonna be king of the pirates.